# LUKA ZORIC

## PROFILE

Extremely motivated to constantly develop my skills and grow professionally. I find meaning in solving complex problems and leading projects to completion. Experienced in building scalable, secure and customer centric solutions, as well as hiring and delegating.

## INTERESTS

## **Coding Languages**

Java, JavaScript, Typescript, HTML/CSS, C, Haskell...

#### Frameworks/Systems

Angular, Bootstrap, TailwindCSS, React, Redux, Node.js, Visual Studio, Git, Docker, AWS, OpenAl...

#### Other

- Computer Vision
- · Architecture & System Design
- Al Chatbots

## EDUCATION

## **Bachelor of Computer Science**

- Enrolled in Feb. 2018
- Majoring in Al and Data Science
- Member of Al Society
- Graduated October 2020

## PERSONAL & BUSINESS PROJECTS

## HazelAl | Personal Al Teacher React, Node, Express.js, Lambda

An Al teacher chatbot that adapts its teaching strategies to enhance the learning experience of users based on their responses.

#### **Skool Clone**

## React, Cloudfront, Lambda, API Gateway, DDB

A platform designed to host and manage communities and courses offering tools for engagement and learning.

## fluxo, ND Agency & Freelance Graphic design Building automated outbound systems for B2B companies and local businesses, optimising Meta Ads, writing copy, selling, managing clients, hiring and outsourcing.

#### Semi-Pro Athlete | Football

Began as Gold Coast United's starting goalkeeper at 19 in the National Premier League, later captained Holland Park Hawks and Broadbeach FC in FQPL1. A 2022 injury led me to switch from playing to focusing on weightlifting, running and business.

## CAREER SUMMARY

## Software Development Engineer II (L5)

Amazon | Apr. 2023 - March. 2024

In my role within Compliance Tech sector, I focused on developing software solutions aimed at enhancing Amazon's capabilities to deter and prevent malicious activities on the selling platform, ensuring a secure and trustworthy environment for our customers.

Served as tech lead for a cross-team project in a completely new space with 5 teams involved. Firstly, developed a high-level solution for services owned by other teams, created a low-level design solution based on the agreed-upon high-level design, delegated work to 3 engineers and delivered.

## Software Development Engineer I (L4)

Amazon | Mar. 2021 - Mar. 2023

As a software development engineer in Amazon's grocery sector, I worked on enhancing customer engagement by developing intuitive front-end solutions for the Amazon Fresh pickup app, alongside robust notification systems supporting both delivery and pickup services.

Given each Amazon Fresh and partner store are unique with their own pickup experience, I served as an SME for the tool used by product and store managers to tailor the pickup process to meet the unique needs of individual locations.

## JavaScript Developer

VirtualMgr | Aug. 2020 - Mar. 2021

- Designing solutions for data visualisation problems within the JSreport environment
- Developing UI/UX solutions and implementing using React, Redux, TypeScript and Node, Express, Docker

## Projects at VirtualMgr:

#### **SmartpassQR**

Node.js, Express, React, MongoDB, Azure

Designed the UI/UX, front end and backend, s

Designed the UI/UX, front end and backend solution for a guest checking app

#### **KPL Recruitment Platform**

React, Node.js, Express, Azure, Docker

Obtained requirements from the stakeholder, designed the full stack solution and independently implemented and deployed product that is still in use.

## Undergraduate Software Engineer AECOM | Nov. 2019 to Feb. 2020

- Designing and creating software solutions to solve problems that fit given requirements
- Building experience in AngularJS and .NET framework
- Larges piece of work done was to implement a theme builder for the EE reporting solution.